<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title></title>
 <link href="http://gistoapp.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://gistoapp.com/"/>
 <updated>2018-09-02T09:55:12+03:00</updated>
 <id>http://gistoapp.com</id>
 <author>
   <name></name>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Gisto version 2</title>
   <link href="http://gistoapp.com/blog/gisto-version-2-in-development"/>
   <updated>2018-02-10T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
   <id>http://gistoapp.com/blog/gisto-version-two</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In the past few months we&amp;rsquo;ve been working hard on the next major Gisto iteration, a complete re-write of Gisto to version 2 with fresh look and functionality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What is the status?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The current status probably should be called beta.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s changed?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everything except the API end point we talking too :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UI completely rewritten with new layout&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Every part of the app rewritten or being rewritten with newer technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Better user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;More search and filtering options&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Probably more&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Development is currently happening in &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/Gisto/Gisto/tree/next&quot;&gt;next&lt;/a&gt; git branch and will be moved to master later on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;Comments, remarks, suggestions and pull request are greatly appriciaetd&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Gisto enterprise mode</title>
   <link href="http://gistoapp.com/blog/gisto-enterprise-mode"/>
   <updated>2015-03-23T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
   <id>http://gistoapp.com/blog/gisto-enterprise-mode</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In the past few months we&amp;rsquo;ve been working hard on the next major release of Gisto which come with a variety of cool features.
This time we want to focus on a major feature that we&amp;rsquo;ve added this release. GitHub Enterprise support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those of you who would love to save snippets of your work but could not do so due to company regulations, or would simply
like to have these snippets available to your co-workers outside of public GitHub, this is for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can now connect to your private GitHub Enterprise using Gisto.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enterprise mode in Gisto allows connecting to your GitHub Enterprise (on-premise) instead of public GitHub.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gisto works the same as it did until now except for a small subset of features that do not make sense on GitHub Enterprise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;How can I use it?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you open Gisto you will notice you will have a GitHub Enterprise toggle button, this is where you can choose to connect to
either public GitHub or your Enterprise instance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When turning on GitHub Enterprise for the first time you will automatically be redirected to the enterprise settings page.
We ask for a few details so we can connect to your GitHub Instance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;API Url - Your Enterprise api URL usually /api/v3 after your instance url which you use to access your Enterprise instance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Client ID&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Client Secret&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Client ID and Client Secret can be acquired by creating an application in your GitHub Enterprise account settings page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog/post-enterprise-mode/step1.png&quot; alt=&quot;Account settings&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Click on Applications on the left sidebar&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog/post-enterprise-mode/step2.png&quot; alt=&quot;Account settings&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Under the Developer Applications click Register new application&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog/post-enterprise-mode/step3.png&quot; alt=&quot;Developer Applications&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the following screen fill the application name as Gisto&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Homepage URL and Authorization callback URL fields may be anything so you can just insert something like &lt;a href=&quot;http://test.com&quot;&gt;http://test.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog/post-enterprise-mode/step4.png&quot; alt=&quot;Register Application&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you created the application you should see the Client ID and Client Secret like in the following screenshot&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog/post-enterprise-mode/step5.png&quot; alt=&quot;Application Details&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Important Note:&lt;/strong&gt; You can share your Client ID and Client Secret with other members of your organization, please note that to allow
notifications being sent only on your organization we had to differentiate between organizations based on the Client ID.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This means that if you want to share a gist with another co-worker you should use the same Client ID.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Sharing and notifications under a private notifications server&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently, all notifications are handled by our servers, the only things we actually send are your username, client id, gist Id and gist
description.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you do not want this data shared across the public internet or have no access to internet from your workstation you can run
the notifications server in premise and connect to that server.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can see all the detailed instructions on how to get the notifications server up and running at the &lt;a href=&quot;/documentation&quot;&gt;Documentation&lt;/a&gt; section.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Nightly builds</title>
   <link href="http://gistoapp.com/blog/nightly-builds"/>
   <updated>2015-02-01T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
   <id>http://gistoapp.com/blog/gisto-nightlies</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Gisto &amp;ldquo;nightly&amp;rdquo; builds are automatic builds triggered by commits to &amp;ldquo;master&amp;rdquo; branch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As of 8th December,2014 we offer nightly build triggered by commits to master branch on GitHub.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note that these are not stable releases. &lt;br&gt;Bugs are possible. Those builds lacks the usual installers you may get in the regular releases.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Nightly&amp;rdquo; builds for all platforms are available at: &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/Gisto/Gisto/releases&quot;&gt;build.gistoapp.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
